<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andradge SPPE</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andradge SPPE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>other-project</title>
      <link>/projects-folder/other-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects-folder/other-project/</guid>
      <description> Hello Worls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>statesRcontiguous</title>
      <link>/projects-folder/statesrcontiguous/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects-folder/statesrcontiguous/</guid>
      <description>statesRcontiguous A useful package for demonstrating choropleth please and more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Wine Quality Exploration</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/02/10/2016-02-10-udacity-project-red-wine-quality/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/02/10/2016-02-10-udacity-project-red-wine-quality/</guid>
      <description>Analysis The scope of this analysis is to understand which chemical properties influence the quality of Red wine.The following data set was utilized in this analysis. This tidy data set contains 1,599 red wines with 11 variables on the chemical properties of the wine.
Load the Data and required Libraries library(ggplot2) library(grid) library(gridExtra) library(psych) library(dplyr) library(data.table) # Local data csv file dataWine &amp;lt;- &amp;quot;../../static/data/wineQualityReds.csv&amp;quot; # Name of unzipped Directory dirFile &amp;lt;- &amp;quot;UCI HAR Dataset&amp;quot; # Download the dataset (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Andradge SPPE(Security &amp;amp; Privacy Prioritization Experts) provides operational best practices and vulnerability remediation prioritization tailored to meet your organization GRC(Governance, Risk and Compliance). We use all tenets of Data Science including Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence and Data Analytics. Our team of experts at Andradge build actionable insight from your data to move your organization towards GRC and operational efficiency.
Our team of experts share stories about their work, datasets and security research of interest on our blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessibility at Andradge </title>
      <link>/accessibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accessibility/</guid>
      <description>Accessibility for all is a core belief for Andradge SPPE(Security &amp;amp; Privacy Prioritization Experts), and something we are constantly trying to improve. We acknowledge that adaptations will be needed for individual’s specific needs. We therefore value both your requests and feedback to help us improve via email info@andradge.com.
We have split our Accessibility information into the following areas:
 Andradge events hosted through Meetups Andradge training courses Andradge website (and blog)   Andradge events through Meetup Training events will be announced on Meetup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessibility at Offsite Locations</title>
      <link>/accessibility_offsite-locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accessibility_offsite-locations/</guid>
      <description>Ask and question us Accessibility for all is a core belief for Andradge SPPE, and something we are constantly trying to improve. We acknowledge that adaptations will be needed for individual’s specific needs. We therefore value both your requests and feedback to help us improve via email info@andradge.com.
Overall accessibility The Wework building has step-free access in most of their buildings.
Training events are hosted in a dedicated room on the ground floor which is fully accessible for those who require a level access route.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consultancy</title>
      <link>/consultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/consultancy/</guid>
      <description>Andradge SPPE(Security &amp;amp; Privacy Prioritization Experts) provides operational best practices and vulnerability remediation prioritization tailored to meet your organization GRC(Governance, Risk and Compliance) using all tenets of Data Science(e.g Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence and Data Analytics). We build actionable insight from your data to move your organization towards GRC and operational efficiency. We have office in Dallas and Atlanta. Email us: info@andradge.com to learn how we can help your reach your GRC goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group Training from Andradge (our offices)</title>
      <link>/training_private_offsite-locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/training_private_offsite-locations/</guid>
      <description>What are the benefits of off-site training?    If your team is distributed across multiple sites it can be really difficult to decide where to hold training on company sites. Dedicated off-site training sites are neutral territory (and Andradge SPPE has lots of hotels nearby 👋)   Re-purposing a conference room at your office for multiple day training courses is often difficult, there’s a temptation to break the training up over multiple weeks or over lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group Training from Andradge (our offices)</title>
      <link>/training_private_your-company-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/training_private_your-company-site/</guid>
      <description>What are the benefits of training at your site?    It’s difficult to get approval and budget for training at dedicated training centers. Training on your company site means zero expenses for staff accommodation.   Sending staff to dedicated training centers means time lost in transit, and potentially time off in lieu if folks are travelling over the weekend. Training starts and finishes when you need it to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>These are projects that the folks at Visible Data are currently working on, both within Visible Data and broader afield.
    OxShef: dataviz OxShef: dataviz is an ambitious partnership between University of Oxford and University of Sheffield to promote and support the development of reproducible interactive visualisations for communicating research datasets and outputs. The collaboration was co-founded by Martin John Hadley, Jez Cope, Anna Krystalli, Tim Snow, and Howard Noble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects (projects.md)</title>
      <link>/projects-folder/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects-folder/projects/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m content/projects/projects.md I have some content here foo
description = &amp;ldquo;Frequently asked questions&amp;rdquo; keywords = [&amp;ldquo;FAQ&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;How do I&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;questions&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;what if&amp;rdquo;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public training at Offsite Locations</title>
      <link>/training_public_offsite-locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/training_public_offsite-locations/</guid>
      <description>Our next training course in Atlanta is a two day course scheduled for Monday 1st April, and focuses on interactive data visualisation with R - CANCELLED.
 Course description  Who is this course for? This course is designed for those who want to create interactive data visualisations with R, including; charts, maps, choropleth, networks, graph and sankey diagrams. In this course you will learn how to:
 Reproducibly read data into R using the tidyverse Wrangle messy data from Excel files into tidy, analysable data with datatables Design interactive dataviz to explore and understand your data  How much R do I need to know?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reproducibility Ratings for Blogposts</title>
      <link>/reproducibility-ratings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reproducibility-ratings/</guid>
      <description>The top and bottom of all blogposts on this site shows a rating for the reproducibility of the content with the following considerations:
 Is the author citable? Is the data citable? Is the code citable (and replicable)?  The rating system is as follows:
   Not reproducible! Complete lack of unique identifier or programmatic access to resource.      Should be reproducible! A potentially volatile link to the resource has been provided, this includes resources like Gists where commercial interests may make them unavailable in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simba M</title>
      <link>/simba-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/simba-m/</guid>
      <description>Simba M  I am a Security, Privacy and Risk professional for 15+ yrs providing expertise and analysis to help enhance organizations’ security posture and to mitigate risk. As such I use all tenets of Data Science(e.g Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence and Data Analytics) for vulnerability remediation prioritization and build actionable insight from that data to move organization to a true SecDevOps for operational efficiency. My tools of choice at present are R, Shiny, Python and Weka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training</title>
      <link>/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/training/</guid>
      <description>Andradge SPPE is passionate about designing and delivering technical training courses and materials that skip unnecessary filler and instead get folks straight into feeling comfortable and confident with importing, wrangling and understanding their datasets.
 On-Demand Training Find our on-demand courses covering R, data science and data visualization on Linkedin Learning and Sage Publishing. 
    
Interested in working with us to develop your course catalog?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>